<html>
<head>
      <title> TLE PT </title>
</head> 
<style>
body {
  background-image: url('sunset.jpg');
  background-repeat: no-repeat;
  background-attachment: fixed;
  background-size: cover;
}
</style>
<font size="70" color="red"><b><center> TODAY </center></b></font>
</body>

	<table border="1" bgcolor="orange" bordercolor="black" cellspacing="3" cellpadding="15">
    <tr>
        <th>ISSUES</th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td align="center">LOCAL NEWS</td>
        <td align="center">The Philippine government said it would prosecute a police officer over the deaths of a mother 
and son, after a video of the point blank shooting went viral in social media, prompting renewed calls against police 
violence and extrajudicial killings.

Senior Master Sergeant Jonel Nuezca is facing double murder charges over the death of Sonya Gregorio and her son, Frank 
Anthony, who were Nuezca’s neighbors in Tarlac province north of the capital, according to the police report. The officer 
has surrendered to authorities, it said.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
        <td align="center">SPORTS</td>
        <td align="center">Brooklyn Nets guard Kyrie Irving is leading the charge to compel the NBA to change its shield 
logo to Kobe Bryant, and he has the backing of the late great's widow, Vanessa Bryant.

In a post to his Instagram page Wednesday, Irving presented an image of Kobe overlayed on the NBA shield, ostensibly his 
choice to supplant the silhouette image modeled after Jerry West, used as the NBA logo since 1969.</td>
    <tr>
	<td align="center">HEALTH</td>
	<td align="center">The Department of Health's (DOH) advisory group has approved the use of Sinovac's COVID-19 
vaccine for Philippine healthcare workers but said those who prefer another brand would not be penalized.

The interim National Immunization Technical Advisory Group (NITAG) made the announcement in a virtual press briefing 
hosted by the DOH on Friday afternoon, February 26.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
	<td align="center">WORLD NEWS</td>
	<td align="center">An intermediate magnitude 4.2 earthquake was reported early morning near Ashkāsham, Ishkāshim, 
Badakhshan, Afghanistan.
According to the United States Geological Survey, the quake hit on Saturday 27 February 2021 at 1:35 am local time at an 
intermediate depth of 106.9 km. The strength of the earthquake may have been tempered by its relative great depth below 
the surface, which makes it feel weaker in absolute terms. The exact magnitude, epicenter, and depth of the quake might be 
revised within the next few hours or minutes as seismologists review data and refine their calculations, or as other 
agencies issue their report.
A second report was later issued by the European-Mediterranean Seismological Centre (EMSC), which listed it as a magnitude 
4.2 earthquake as well.
Towns or cities near the epicenter where the quake might have been felt as very weak shaking include Ashkāsham (pop. 
12,100) located 30 km from the epicenter, Ishqoshim (pop. 26,000) 37 km away, and Jurm (pop. 12,100) 71 km away.</td>
    </tr>
</table>
<br>
<body>
<font size="70" color="blue"><b><center> TOMORROW </center></b></font>
<p align="center">
<img src="image of hope.png">
<br>
<br>
<center>
   <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cn4rp5gXtLU&feature=share&fbclid=IwAR08GGMHlPps3En7rNxe0uz4pqMHJq59_hvGeJYtGwLu6rUhBeE-OzM1hNw> DON'T LOSE HOPE</a>
</center>
</body>
</html>